CoICT digital.
The main aim of this project is to improve the management of college business processes through the support of a CoICT Digital System. ICTs are widely deployed in Tanzanian Universities, following the University of Dar es salaam (UDSM) that has successfully employed ICT systems such as ARIS, LMS and FYP, there is a need for digitising some other activities that are performed manually. The activities digitized in this project include course allocation to lectures, invigilator allocation, course evaluation by students, teaching and learning monitoring and alumni records management.

System Functions
System functions include: 
● Management of alumni records 
● Management of course evaluation 
● Teaching and learning monitoring 
● Management of course allocation 
● Allocate exam invigilator

Getting Started
To get started with exploring CoictDigital you can clone the repository and deploy it in your server. 
The database is called coict_digital.sql and it needs to be installed too and run in your server. To see the functionalities of the system you need to login as a user of the system. 
User 1- Student Username: reg_no(from database table users) Password: surname(from database table users) 
User 2- Staff Username: email(from database table users) Password: surname(from database table users) 
User 3- Admin Username: admin@udsm.ac.tz Password: admin
User 4- head of department Username: hod@udsm.ac.tz Password: mdeme